Tufts Africa Forum Records UA035
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Africa Forum Records
2000 -- 2004
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Africa Forum
UA035
0.5 Linear Feet 1 box
Arrangement
This collection is organized in one series: Subject Files.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the subject files of the Tufts Africa Forum Faculty Convener, Jeanne Marie Penvenne.
Related Materials
UA053, Black Cultural Center Seminar at Tufts records, DCA
Biographical / Historical
In 2000 Vice Provost June Aprille began to identify and forge closer contact among Tufts faculty, researchers and students who have professional interest and expertise in Africa and the African diaspora. In collaboration with faculty and administrators in Arts and Sciences, Engineering, Fletcher, the School of Medicine, Veterinary Medicine, Nutrition and Health Sciences and Tufts various centers, Aprille gathered data on Africana projects university wide and proposed a workshop to explore the extent of Tufts professional connections around the African continent, to exchange ideas, to identify synergistic collaborations and to determine if and in what form workshop participants might want to pursue exchange and collaboration within Tufts.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
Foreign affairs
- Subject Files, 2000 -- 2004; UA035.001; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of subject files created by Tufts Africa Forum Faculty Convener, Jeanne Marie Penvenne.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged as found.
  Conditions Governing Access
  20 years from date of creation.
  - One Campus/One University Initative, 2003; UA035.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Photographs TAF, 2003 -- 2004; UA035.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - TAF Annual Reports, 2002 -- 2004; UA035.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - TAF Visitors, 2003; UA035.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - TAF Institutional Memory, 2001 -- 2002; UA035.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Africa Forum, 2001; UA035.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - TAF Spring Workshop, 2004; UA035.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - TAF Closing-Emails, 2004; UA035.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - African Solutions to African Problems?, 2004; UA035.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - TAF Working Stuff, 2004; UA035.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - TAF Panel, 2003; UA035.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - TAF Workshop, 2002; UA035.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Tufts African Forum, 2001; UA035.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - TAF, 2000 -- 2001; UA035.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Steve Cohen - TAF, 2002; UA035.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - TAF - Joanna Friedman, 2002; UA035.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - TAF Fall 2002 Mtg, UA035.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - MOU Marlene/Dan, 2001 -- 2002; UA035.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Linkage - Dar Es Salaam = Grant, 2002; UA035.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - TAF Listserve, 2002; UA035.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - TAF - Content, 2002; UA035.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - TAF Survey, 2002; UA035.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - TAF Correspondence, 2002; UA035.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - AT Faculty Grant TAF, 2002; UA035.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - TAF Addis Ababa Mtg, 2002; UA035.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - TAF Reimbursements/Budget, 2003 -- 2004; UA035.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - TAF, 2002 -- 2003; UA035.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Bennish Principles, 2002; UA035.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - TAF Annual Report, 2002 -- 2003; UA035.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - 14 Feb TAF, 2003; UA035.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - TAF - IRB Workshop, 2003; UA035.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - IRB-Shaw, 2003; UA035.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - TAF - Annual Report, 2003 -- 2004; UA035.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - TAF Budget and Personnel, 2002 -- 2003; UA035.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - TAF Brochure, 2002; UA035.001.001.00035 (Box 1)